# Jonah Pearce

(650) 619-5986 ◆ <u>Jpearce1993@gmail.com</u>

LinkedIn: <u>Jonah Pearce</u> ◆ GitHub: <u>Jpearce1993</u>

A detail oriented web developer with extensive leadership and teamwork experience. Well versed in various web development coding languages and recognized for responsibility, approachability, organization, and the ability to learn.

# **Top Key Skills**

CSS

HTML

Javascript

Git

Microsoft Office Program

#### Education

 Front-End Engineer Career Path Codecademy

(January 2021 - Present)

• A.S. Computer & Information Science with Concentration in App Development

College of San Mateo (March 2020 - November 2020)

• A.S. Fire Technology College of San Mateo

(March 2011 - November 2014)

## **Experience**

Helitack Crewmember, CALFIRE

Los Gatos, CA (May 2018- Nov 2019)

- Worked and lived alongside 8 crew members at Alma Station 13 & 31.
- Maintained, trained alongside, and fought fire with a CALFIRE UH-1H helicopter.
- Responded to incidents ranging from fire suppression to aerial rescue operations.
- Maintained fire suppression, leadership, medical, and situational awareness skills on a daily basis through training scenarios and group led lessons.
- Led and completed daily physical training regimens alongside crewmembers.
- Assigned and completed daily station maintenance projects ranging from cleaning to construction.
- Performed Crew Resource Management duties regularly, varying from debriefings to maintaining crew cohesion.
- Assigned and completed joint force training with neighboring agencies on a regular basis.

#### Firefighter 1, CALFIRE

Santa Clara Unit (March 2015 - May 2018)

- Worked and lived alongside 5 to 12 crew members at CALFIRE stations 14 & 16.
- Responded to emergencies varying from medical incidents to traffic collisions.
- Regularly volunteered time to help the community at local events.
- Maintained community relationships with outreach and fire prevention activities.

### **Volunteer Experience**

### **Explorer Advisor, CALFIRE**

(September 2011 - March 2015)

- Performed various trainings alongside CALFIRE Station 17.
- Led community based education programs on fire safety.